# SHU TANOUE

### FRONTEND DEVELOPER

### CONTACT

Address: Vancouver, BC Phone: (236) 862-3022 Mail: shutanoue@gmail.com LinkedIn: shu-tanoue-0099

GitHub: shu-tanoue

Portfolio: shutanoue.com

## TECHNICAL SKILLS

### **Specialties**

JavaScript, HTML5, CSS3, WordPress, and Sass

#### Other skills

React.js, jQuery, Bootstrap, PHP, and Git

#### **EDUCATION**

## Web & Mobile Application Development, Diploma

Cornerstone International Community College of Canada Vancouver, BC Jan 2020 - Jan 2021

React.js, JavaScript, HTML, CSS, Sass, Node.js, and Git

### SUMMARY

well trained junior web developer able to design and develop websites using the latest programming languages. Specializes in React. is and JavaScript. Constantly strives to better manage technology and development projects. Takes action and initiative in teamwork.

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

### WEB PRODUCTION EIGHT, JAPAN

Remote, Sep 2020 - Present

- Built a gourmet food information landing page using JavaScript, HTML, and CSS
- Developed a kayaking company website using WordPress, JavaScript, HTML, CSS, jQuery, and PHP
- Deployed and released websites using Git and FTP

## Government Official Self-Defense Forces

Kumamoto, Japan Apr 2013 - Apr 2015

#### **PROJECTS**

## WEST VANCOUVER CRICKET CLUB COMPANY WEBSITE (HTML, CSS, JAVASCRIPT, SASS)

A client project cricket club website created by team

development.

## COMPANY WEBSITE PROJECT FOR PRO CALIBER LACROSSE CLUB

(HTML, CSS, SASS, JQUERY, JAVASCRIPT)

A client project for a pro lacrosse team website created by team development.

#### **VANCOUVER WASHROOM MAP**

(REACT, JAVASCRIPT, BOOTSTRAP, HTML, CSS)

Vancouver washroom maps and washroom list website as an owned media using React.js, Bootstrap, HTML, CSS, Sass, JavaScript, and Google Maps API